question_data = [{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The main playable character of the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot; is a monster.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"St. Louis is the capital of the US State Missouri.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Politics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"One of Barack Obama&#039;s United States presidential campaign slogan&#039;s was &quot;Yes We Can&quot;.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]